sharecoupons.info 2014-08-24

# Privacy Policy, GoDaddy promo code

[](http://sharecoupons.info/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Privacy-Policy.jpg)If you  have any questions about our privacy policy, please  [contact us](http://sharecoupons.info/about-us/ "Contact Us"), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by sharecoupons.info  

* **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, the site makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

* **Cookies and Web Beacons**

http://sharecoupons.info does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

* **Our Coupons**

When you visit our Sites or download and install our coupon printing software, toolbar, or mobile applications on your computer or other device, we may collect and store information about that device that helps us manage our products and services, deliver a more customized experience for you, and detect and prevent coupon fraud.  
A device identifier remains associated with your computer even after uninstalling the coupon printer software. This identifier is used primarily to prevent coupon fraud and does not collect personally identifiable information.

* **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our homepage so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
